trojan-killer.net 2016-06-27

# Privacy Policy | Gridinsoft

### 1\. Personal Information.

In some circumstances, GridinSoft may request personal information from you, like your name, email address. Your response to these inquiries is voluntary. GridinSoft uses this information for business purposes, such as informing you about product releases or other events that can assist you in your business or order processing.

### 2\. Domain information and statistics.

GridinSoft automatically collects information about visitors and site activities. The information is stored on an aggregate basis and used to improve its Web-based and business offerings.

### 3\. Disclosure to third parties.

Any information collected from you will not be sold, rented or disclosed in any way to any third parties. In some circumstances, we may ask your permission to use your personal information for business purposes.

### 4\. Contacting You.

Sometimes we send you email messages in order to inform you about new products, available updates to existing products or other information you may find valuable for your business. You can decide not to receive emails from us and unsubscribe from our mailing list. However, the unsubscribing process is not immediate. We may also contact you for administrative purposes despite the fact that you unsubscribed from the mailing list.

### 5\. Cookies and Other Tracking Technologies.

Some of our web pages utilize cookies and other tracking technologies. Tracking technologies may record information such as Internet domain, host names, Internet protocol (IP) addresses. All information recorded by cookies or tracking technologies is used to improve our Web site and in administrative purposes only.

### 6\. Consent.

By using this Web site, you consent to the terms of our Online Privacy Policy. If you do not agree to our Privacy Policy, please stop using this site.  
GridinSoft reserves the right to change, modify or update this statement at any time without notice.

Please, direct any questions regarding Privacy Statement to [support@gridinsoft.com](mailto:support@gridinsoft.com).
